[{"answer": "I was gonna say hypnotism...but I like that. It's out of the fucking box. We just strap one to some motherfucker's chest, like we did to those watermelons. Think you can you build some kinda bomb vest", "docId": "30-Minutes-or-Less.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I'm pretty sure this is exactly how a millionaire would do it. And the beauty of it i", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Hey, if you guys had that twin ESP shit this would be a completely different situation. There'd be logistical problems", "docId": "30-Minutes-or-Less.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "You look like a lot of people. You're a normal looking dude", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "You? An adult? Sort of stretching the term", "docId": "30-Minutes-or-Less.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Take back? Will, you got kicked out of junior college for punching a professor that made fun of some poem you wrote", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Why are you doing this to me? I don't have any money", "docId": "30-Minutes-or-Less.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Okay. Sure, man. Whatever you say. I'll go sell my car. I'll get you like a thousand bucks", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "The that place on that place. 30", "docId": "30-Minutes-or-Less.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Yeah, the one across the street from the Olive Garden", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I am not fucking around here. Two guys did this to me. And if I don't rob that bank in time this thing is gonna blow", "docId": "30-Minutes-or-Less.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Seriously", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Fuck you. She's in the eighth grade", "docId": "30-Minutes-or-Less.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "She doesn't call me", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "my friend, my friend. Please. I'm begging you here. I need you on this. If I do it alone, I'm dead. 45", "docId": "30-Minutes-or-Less.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "That was a moment of weakness.  Yes. I'll fucking cry again if that's what it takes", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Everybody put your hands in the air", "docId": "30-Minutes-or-Less.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Actually, listen to him and get on the fucking ground", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Just take it easy, man! 64", "docId": "30-Minutes-or-Less.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "What the fuck does that mean? I'm not a hero! Or a cowboy", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "But it hurts so bad", "docId": "30-Minutes-or-Less.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "This is an awful story! This isn't a bank error in my favor! I got shot", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "There's a 100 grand in there. 100 fucking grand. Which we stole. From a bank", "docId": "30-Minutes-or-Less.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I threatened to blow up a cop.  And you never said", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Why? So he can fuck around again, and I wind up dead, anyway? No. I'd rather just sit here. I want to die right here on this couch", "docId": "30-Minutes-or-Less.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "How do we do that? Pizza boy's obviously got some kinda death wish", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "It's been half an hour", "docId": "30-Minutes-or-Less.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "In another 30 minutes I'm calling the bomb squad", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I don't know what you're talking about. Just take the money", "docId": "30-Minutes-or-Less.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I'm not a loose end", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I will. And then I'm gonna tie up the two loose ends in the gorilla masks", "docId": "30-Minutes-or-Less.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "You're a fucking idiot. You are as loose as ends get", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "\"His time was up", "docId": "30-Minutes-or-Less.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": " He's not that kind of guy. He doesn't think about the future. Ever", "qsentId": 34}]